Now that we've covered many of the mechanics of Pandas, I want to stop and
現在我們已經涵蓋了Pandas的許多機制，我想停下來
talk for a moment about data types and scales.
談談資料類型(type)和尺度(scale)。
We've already seen that Pandas supports a number of different computational data
我們已經看到Pandas支持許多不同的計算資料類型，
types such as strings, integers and floating point numbers.
如字串，整數和浮點數。
What this doesn't capture is what we call the scale of the data.
這不能抓到我們所說的資料尺度
Let's say that we have a data frame of students and
假設我們有一個DataFrame的學生和
their academic levels such as being in grade 1 or grade 2 and grade 3.
他們的學校年級，如1年級，2年級和3年級。
There's a difference between a student in grade 1 and a student in grade 2, the same
1年級的學生和2年級的學生有所不同，一樣的
as the difference between a student in grade 8 and a student in grade 9.
8年級和9年級的學生有所不同。
Well let's think about the final exam scores these students might get
讓我們考慮這些學生可能獲得的期末考試成績
on assignments.
的作業。
Is the difference between an A and
A和A-之間的差異與
an A minus the same as the difference between an A minus and a B plus?
A-和B+之間的差值相同嗎？
At the University of Michigan at least, the answer is usually no.
在密歇根大學，至少答案通常不是。
We've intuitively seen some different scales, and
我們直觀地看到了一些不同的尺度，
as we move through data cleaning and statistical analysis and
當我們進行數據清理和統計分析和
machine learning, it's important to clarify our knowledge and terminology.
機器學習時，重要的是要澄清我們的知識和術語。
As a data scientist there four scales that it's worth knowing.
作為一個數據科學家，有四個尺度，值得了解。
The first is a ratio scale.
第一個是比率(ratio)尺度。
In the ratio scale the measurements units are equally spaced and mathematical
在比率尺度中，測量單位相等間隔，數學
operations, such as subtract, division, and multiplication are all valid.
運算（如減法，除法和乘法）都是有效的。
Good examples of ratio scale measurements might be the height and weight.
比率尺度測量的良好例子可能是高度和重量。
The next scale is the interval scale.
下一個尺度是間隔(interval)尺度。
In the interval scale the measurement units are equally spaced
在間隔尺度中，測量單元相等間隔。
like the ratio scale.
與比率尺度相同
But there's no clear absence of value.
沒有明確的缺乏數值。。
That is there isn't a true zero, and so operation such as multiplication and
那就是沒有一個真正的零，所以運算如乘法和
division are not valid.
除法是無效的。
An example of the interval scale might be the temperatures measured in Celsius or
間隔尺度的一個例子可能是測量的溫度，以攝氏或
Fahrenheit.
華氏的溫度。
Since there's never an absence of temperature and
因為沒有沒有的溫度，
0 degrees is a meaningful value of temperature.
0度是一個有意義的溫度值。
The direction on a campus might be another good example where 0 degrees on the campus
羅盤的方向可能是另一個很好的例子，羅盤內的0度
doesn't indicate a lack of direction.
並不表示缺乏方向。
For most of the work you do at data mining, the differences between
對於在數據挖掘中所做的大部分工作，差異在
the ratio and interval scales might not be clearly apparent or
比率和間隔尺度之間，可能不是那麼明顯或
important than the algorithm you're applying.
重要，比較於您所使用的算法。
But it's important to have this clear in your mind when you're applying advanced
但重要的是在你的心中要清楚，當你應用在先進
statistical tests.
的統計測試時
The next scale is the ordinal scale, and this is also important.
下一個尺度是序數(ordinal)尺度，這也很重要。
In the ordinal scale the order of values is important but
在序數尺度上，值的順序是重要的，
the differences between the values are not equally spaced.
但是值之間的差異並不等間隔。
Here is a grading method that is used in many classes at the University of Michigan
這裡是密西根大學許多課程中使用的一個打成績分數 的方法，
as a great example, where letter grades are given with pluses and minuses.
是一個很好的例子，其中字母成績被賦予了加減。
But when you compare this to percentage values you see that a letter by itself
但是，當您將此與百分比值進行比較時，您會看到只有字母本身
covers 4% of the available grades and that a letter with a plus or
涵蓋了4％的可用成績，而字母有加號或
minus is usually just 4% for the available grades.
減號的通常只有可用成績的3％。
Based on this, it would be odd if there were as many students who received
基於此，那就是奇怪了，如果有同樣多的學生拿
an A plus or A minus as there were who received a straight A.
到A+或A-的，和那些拿到只是A的.
Ordinal data is very common in machine learning and
有序數據在機器學習中非常普遍，
can sometimes be a challenge to work with.
有時候是一個挑戰。
The last scale I'll mention is the nominal scale which is
最後我會提到的尺度是名義(nominal)尺度
often just called categorical data.
往往只是被稱為分類(categorical)數據。
Here the names of teams in a sport might be good example.
這裡的體育隊的名稱可能是很好的例子。
There are a limited number of teams but changing their order or
團隊的數目有限的,而改變他們的順序或
playing mathematical function to them is meaningless.
將數學函數應用到他們是毫無意義的。
Categorical values are very common and we generally refer to categories
分類值是很常見，我們通常指類別，
where there are only two possible values as binary.
那裡有只有兩個可能的值為二進制值。
So why did I stop talking about Pandas and jump into this discussion of scale.
那麼為什麼我停止談論Pandas呢，並跳上這個尺度的討論。
Well, given how important they are in statistics and
那麼，鑑於他們的重要性在統計學和
machine learning, Pandas has a number of interesting functions to
機器學習中，Pandas有很多有趣的功能來
deal with converting between measurement scales.
處理測量尺度之間的轉換。
Let's start first with nominal data, which in Pandas is called categorical data.
我們先從名義(nominal)數據開始，在Pandas被稱為分類(category)數據。
Panda is actually has a built in type for categorical data and you could
Pandas實際上具有內置類型的分類數據，您可以
set a column of your data to categorical data by using the as type method.
使用astype方法將數據列設置為分類數據。
As type tries to change the underlying type of your data,
astype嘗試更改您的數據的底層類型，
in this case to category data.
在這種情況下改到類別數據。
You can further change this to ordinal data by passing in an ordered flags set to
您可以進一步將其更改為序數(ordinal)數據，通過將ordered標誌設置為
true and passing in the categories in an ordered fashion.
true，並以有序的方式傳遞類別來。
Here's an example.
這裡有個例子，這裡有個例子，
Let's create a data frame of letter grades in the descending order.
讓我們創建一個DataFrame按照降序的字母級別。
We can also set an index value of some more course grain measure.
我們還可以設定一些更粗略措施的索引值。
Now when we instruct Pandas to render this as categorical data, we see that the D
現在當我們指示Pandas將其作為分類數據時，我們看到
type has been set as category and that there are 11 different categories.
dtype已被設置為類別(category)，並且有11個不同的類別。
If we want to indicate to Pandas that this data is in a logical order,
如果我們想要向Pandas表明這資料是按邏輯順序，
we pass the ordered equals true flag and
我們通過ordered=True設置標誌和
we see those reflected in the category D type using the less than sign.
我們看到這個數據反映在類別dtype中，使用小於(<)符號。
What can you do with this?
你能用這個做什麼？
Well, ordinal data has ordering so it can help you with the Boolean masking.
那麼，序數(ordinal)數據有一個排序，所以它可以幫助你進行布林屏蔽(boolean mask)。
For instance, if we have our list of grades and we compared them with a C.
例如，如果我們有我們的成績列表，我們將它們與C進行了比較。
If we did this lexographically, we would that a C+ and
如果我們根據字典順序來作，那麼C+和
a C- are both actually greater than a C.
C-都實際上大於C.
Instead of coding each of these to something which is lexographical,
與其將這些一個接一個編碼，本來是根據字典順序的
like a number, we can indicate that there's a clear order to the data.
，就像數字一樣，我們可以指出數據有明確的順序。
And then broadcasting will work as we expect.
然後廣播會如我們所預期的。
We can then use a certain set of mathematical operators like minimum,
然後，我們可以使用一組數學運算，如最小值，
maximum and others on the ordinal data.
最大值和其他數學運算在序數(ordinal)數據。
Sometimes it's useful to represent categorical values as each being a column
有時是有用的，因為每個分類都是列，去表示分類值，
with a true or a false as to whether that category applies.
用true或false值，取決於是否適用於該類別。
This is especially common in feature extraction,
這在特徵(feature)提取(extraction)中特別常見，
which is a topic in the third course in this specialization.
這是在專業化課程的第三個中的一個課題。
Variables with a Boolean value are typically called dummy variables.
變數用布林(boolean)值的通常稱為虛擬(dummy)變數。
And pandas has a built-in function called get dummies,
Pandas有一個內置的功能，稱為get_dummies，
which will convert the values of a single column into multiple columns of 0's and
它將單個列的值轉換成多個列的0
1's, indicating the presence of a dummy variable.
和1，表示虛擬變量的存在。
There's one more function on scales that I'd like to talk about.
還有一個尺度功能，我想談談的。
And that's on reducing a value which is on the interval or
那就是轉換一個在間隔尺度或
ratio scale, like a number grade, into one that is categorical like a letter grade.
比率尺度的值，像數字等級，到分類尺度，像一個字母級別一樣。
Now, this might seem a bit counter intuitive to you since you're losing
現在，這似乎有點反直覺，由於您失去了
information about the value.
有關該值的信息。
But it's useful on a couple of places.
但它在幾個地方很有用。
First, if you're visualizing the frequencies of categories, and
首先，如果您可視化類別的頻率，
this can be an extremely useful approach and
這可能是一個非常有用的方法，
histograms are regularly used with converted interval or racial data.
而且直方圖(histogram)經常用於轉換了的間隔(interval)或比率(ratio)數據。
And we'll take a look at histograms in the second course in this specialization.
我們將在這個專業化的第二個課程中看一下直方圖。
Second, if you're using a machine learning classification approach on data,
其次，如果你使用機器學習分類方法處理數據，
then you need to be using categorical data.
則你需要使用分類數據。
So reducing dimensionality is useful there too.
所以降低維度(dimensionality)也是有用的。
panda says a function called cut, which takes in argument which is some real
Pandas有一個名為cut的功能，它接受一個參數，這參數是一些像陣列結構
like structure of a column or a data frame or a series.
像是一列或是 資料幀或是系列的結構
It also takes a number of bins to be used and all bins are kept at equal spacing.
它還需要使用多個箱子(bins)，並且所有箱子保持相等的間距。
Let's go back to our census data for an example.
我們回到我們的人口普查數據的例子。
We saw that we could group by state,
我們看到我們可以按州分組，
then aggregate to get a list of the average county size by state.
然後總匯到州的縣級平均人口名單。
If we further apply cut to this with say 10 bins, we can see that
如果我們進一步用cut向這名單，用10個bins，我們可以看到，
the states listed as categoricals using the average county size.
我們可以看到州列出了使用縣級平均人口的分類。
Here we see the states like Alabama and Alaska fall into the same category, while
在這裡，我們看到像Alabama州和Alaska州這樣的州屬於同一類別，
California and the District of Colombia fall into a very different category.
而California州和District of Colombia同屬於一個非常不同的類別。
Now, cutting is just one way to build categories from your data, and
現在，cut只是從數據中構建類別的一種方法，
there's many other methods.
還有許多其他方法。
For instance, cut gives you interval data,
例如，cut給你間隔(interval)數據，
where the spacing between each category is equal sized.
每個類別之間的間距大小相等。
But sometimes you want to form categories based on frequency.
但有時你想根據頻率來形成分類。
You want the number of items in each bin to be the same,
您希望每個倉(bin)中的物品數量相同，
instead of the spacing between bins.
而不是倉之間的間距。
It really depends on the shape of your data and
它真的取決於你的數據的形式和
what you're planning to do with it.
你打算做什麼。
And we'll look at some examples of this in the graphing and charting course for
我們將看一些例子在繪圖和製圖課程
those of you who are enrolled in the specialization.
為那些註冊在專業化課的。
That's it for this module of the course.
這就是本模組的課程。
There's a programming assignment to test your knowledge of this module's content
還有一個程式的作業來測試你對本模組內容瞭解
and I'll see you back in the next module as a wrap up where we'll talk more
回頭見，在下一個課程為總結，在那裡我們將詳細討論
about statistics and set up some basics for comparing results of analysis.
關於統計和建立一些基本的分析結果比較。